mobitemedia.com 2016-05-11

# Mobite

### Privacy Policy

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the www.mobite.com and Mobite Media Group and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Mobite Media Group include www.mobite.com and Mobile. The Mobile website is a Mobile Affiliate Network site. By using the Mobile website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement. 

**Collection of your Personal Information**

We do not collect personally identifiable information from our users. We may gather personal or non-personal information in the future. 

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Mobile. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Mobile website. 

Mobile encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Mobile so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Mobile is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Mobile website. 

**Security of your Personal Information**

Mobile secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. 

**Children Under Thirteen**

Mobile does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website. 

**Opt-Out & Unsubscribe**

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Mobile by contacting us here: 

\- Web page: www.mobite.com 

\- Email: Contact@Mobite.com 

\- Phone: +9720722159412 

**Changes to this Statement**

Mobile will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Mobile encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Mobile is protecting your information. 

**Contact Information**

Mobile welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Mobile has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Mobile at: 

Mobite Media Group 

HaBarzel 21 

Tel-Aviv, Israel. 

Email Address: 

Contact@Mobite.com 

Telephone number: 

+9720722159412 

Effective as of November 04, 2014
